("Wherever You Will Go" by The Calling)
♪ So lately been wondering ♪
♪ Who will be there to take my place ♪
♪ When I'm gone you'll need love ♪
♪ To light the shadows on your face ♪
♪ If a great wave shall fall ♪
♪ And fall upon us all ♪
♪ Then between the sand and stone ♪
♪ Could you make it on your own ♪
♪ If I could then I would ♪
♪ I'll go wherever you will go ♪
♪ Way up high or down low ♪
♪ And maybe I'll find out ♪
♪ A way to make it back someday ♪
♪ To watch you to guide you ♪
♪ Through the darkest of your days ♪
♪ If a great wave shall fall ♪
♪ And fall upon us all ♪
♪ Well then I hope there's
someone out there ♪
♪ Who can bring me back to you ♪
♪ If I could then I would ♪
♪ I'll go wherever you will go ♪
♪ Way up high or down low ♪
♪ Run away with my heart ♪
♪ Run away with my hope ♪
♪ Run away with my love ♪
♪ I know now just quite how ♪
♪ My life and love might still go on ♪
♪ In your heart in your mind ♪
♪ I'll stay with you for all of time ♪
♪ If I could then I would ♪
♪ I'll go wherever you will go ♪
♪ Way up high or down low ♪
♪ If I could turn back time ♪
♪ I'll go wherever you will go ♪
♪ If I could make you mine ♪